{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079368644","data":{"timestamp":" 947079368643"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 34c2d733-8815-4a73-8aa1-704a57057fc1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079380102","data":{"timestamp":" 947079380101"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KALAMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" KALAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079383565","data":{"timestamp":" 947079383565"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KALAMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079385111","data":{"timestamp":" 947079385111"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIBOKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079388358","data":{"timestamp":" 947079388358"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIBOKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079389954","data":{"timestamp":" 947079389954"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KICHWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079393967","data":{"timestamp":" 947079393967"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KICHWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079395566","data":{"timestamp":" 947079395566"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIJIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" KIJIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079399365","data":{"timestamp":" 947079399364"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIJIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" KIJIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079400942","data":{"timestamp":" 947079400942"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITENGE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" KITENGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079404435","data":{"timestamp":" 947079404434"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITENGE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079406023","data":{"timestamp":" 947079406018"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" KITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079408829","data":{"timestamp":" 947079408829"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" KITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079410451","data":{"timestamp":" 947079410451"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079413541","data":{"timestamp":" 947079413541"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" START_KOBE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079415364","data":{"timestamp":" 947079415364"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079416953","data":{"timestamp":" 947079416953"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIPEPEO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEPEO"," userResponse":" KIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079421042","data":{"timestamp":" 947079421042"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIPEPEO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEPEO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079422586","data":{"timestamp":" 947079422586"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIKOMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079426007","data":{"timestamp":" 947079426007"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KIKOMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079427581","data":{"timestamp":" 947079427581"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOFIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079430925","data":{"timestamp":" 947079430925"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOFIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079432492","data":{"timestamp":" 947079432491"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUCHAKURO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHAKURO"," userResponse":" KUCHAKURO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079440807","data":{"timestamp":" 947079440807"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUCHAKURO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHAKURO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079442376","data":{"timestamp":" 947079442376"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KONDOO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079446044","data":{"timestamp":" 947079446044"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KONDOO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079447610","data":{"timestamp":" 947079447610"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUNDI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNDI"," userResponse":" KUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079451576","data":{"timestamp":" 947079451575"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUNDI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079453154","data":{"timestamp":" 947079453154"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" KOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079458762","data":{"timestamp":" 947079458762"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KOMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079460336","data":{"timestamp":" 947079460336"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KINYOZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" KINYOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079466074","data":{"timestamp":" 947079466074"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KINYOZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079467645","data":{"timestamp":" 947079467645"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAROTI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079471890","data":{"timestamp":" 947079471890"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAROTI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079473463","data":{"timestamp":" 947079473462"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITABU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079477126","data":{"timestamp":" 947079477126"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KITABU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079478687","data":{"timestamp":" 947079478687"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079483197","data":{"timestamp":" 947079483197"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079484255","data":{"timestamp":" 947079484255"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUTEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079484774","data":{"timestamp":" 947079484774"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUTEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079571707","data":{"timestamp":" 947079571707"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" KUTEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079571816","data":{"timestamp":" 947079571816"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" 7f4e0fa2-22ef-4b15-8576-eb585fe4b3d5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" KUTEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079585719","data":{"timestamp":" 947079585719"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" af9c7857-bb2a-4c26-94a7-403ebb1a1bee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079586559","data":{"timestamp":" 947079586559"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" af9c7857-bb2a-4c26-94a7-403ebb1a1bee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_3v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079603629","data":{"timestamp":" 947079603629"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" af9c7857-bb2a-4c26-94a7-403ebb1a1bee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_3v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079631271","data":{"timestamp":" 947079631271"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" eb67b188-64cc-4bf2-ba80-3b8e1bc67b37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani_huyu-huu-joto-nani"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" joto"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079633974","data":{"timestamp":" 947079633974"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" eb67b188-64cc-4bf2-ba80-3b8e1bc67b37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani_huyu-huu-joto-nani"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" nani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079655543","data":{"timestamp":" 947079655542"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" eb67b188-64cc-4bf2-ba80-3b8e1bc67b37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani_huu-nani-hao-ghafla"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" ghafla"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079658222","data":{"timestamp":" 947079658222"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" eb67b188-64cc-4bf2-ba80-3b8e1bc67b37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani_huu-nani-hao-ghafla"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" hao"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079660912","data":{"timestamp":" 947079660911"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" eb67b188-64cc-4bf2-ba80-3b8e1bc67b37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani_huu-nani-hao-ghafla"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" nani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079693796","data":{"timestamp":" 947079693796"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" eb67b188-64cc-4bf2-ba80-3b8e1bc67b37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gari_au-gari-simu-mkono"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" gari"," userResponse":" au"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079696533","data":{"timestamp":" 947079696532"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" eb67b188-64cc-4bf2-ba80-3b8e1bc67b37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gari_au-gari-simu-mkono"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" gari"," userResponse":" gari"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079706308","data":{"timestamp":" 947079706308"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" eb67b188-64cc-4bf2-ba80-3b8e1bc67b37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" gari_au-gari-simu-mkono"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079706400","data":{"timestamp":" 947079706400"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" eb67b188-64cc-4bf2-ba80-3b8e1bc67b37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi ____________!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" NAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079739664","data":{"timestamp":" 947079739664"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" cef086f9-439a-4d26-ad21-7869c9a7bfc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani_gani-jambo-ambayo-nani"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" gani"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079742604","data":{"timestamp":" 947079742604"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" cef086f9-439a-4d26-ad21-7869c9a7bfc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani_gani-jambo-ambayo-nani"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" jambo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079745304","data":{"timestamp":" 947079745304"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" cef086f9-439a-4d26-ad21-7869c9a7bfc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani_gani-jambo-ambayo-nani"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" ambayo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079748853","data":{"timestamp":" 947079748853"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" cef086f9-439a-4d26-ad21-7869c9a7bfc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani_gani-jambo-ambayo-nani"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" nani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079791411","data":{"timestamp":" 947079791410"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" cef086f9-439a-4d26-ad21-7869c9a7bfc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani_nani-kasi-huu-je"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" nani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079819902","data":{"timestamp":" 947079819902"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" cef086f9-439a-4d26-ad21-7869c9a7bfc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gari_simu-gari-punde-pumzi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" gari"," userResponse":" pumzi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079822716","data":{"timestamp":" 947079822716"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" cef086f9-439a-4d26-ad21-7869c9a7bfc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gari_simu-gari-punde-pumzi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" gari"," userResponse":" punde"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079825394","data":{"timestamp":" 947079825394"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" cef086f9-439a-4d26-ad21-7869c9a7bfc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gari_simu-gari-punde-pumzi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" gari"," userResponse":" gari"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079841125","data":{"timestamp":" 947079841125"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" cef086f9-439a-4d26-ad21-7869c9a7bfc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" gari_simu-gari-punde-pumzi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079841212","data":{"timestamp":" 947079841211"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000105_163558"," gameId":" cef086f9-439a-4d26-ad21-7869c9a7bfc0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi ____________!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}